An official website of the United States government Here’s how you know

**Official websites use .gov**  
A **.gov** website belongs to an official government organization in the United States.

**Secure .gov websites use HTTPS**  
A **lock** () or **https://** means you’ve safely connected to the .gov website. Share sensitive information only on official, secure websites.

    Created by the U.S. Congress in 1970, the National Credit Union Administration is an independent federal agency that insures deposits at federally insured credit unions, protects the members who own credit unions, and charters and regulates federal credit unions.

    The NCUA protects the safety and soundness of the credit union system by identifying, monitoring and reducing risks to the National Credit Union Share Insurance Fund. Backed by the full faith and credit of the United States, the Share Insurance Fund provides up to $250,000 of federal share insurance to millions of account holders in all federal credit unions and the overwhelming majority of state-chartered credit unions.

    The NCUA’s economists and analysts compile data on the credit union system’s financial performance, merger activity, changes in credit union chartering and fields of membership, as well as broader economic trends affecting credit unions. Users can find information on a single credit union or analyze broader nation-wide trends.

    The NCUA provides a number of support services to the credit union system, such as providing training, grants and loans, chartering, and field-of-membership services; maintaining the health and stability of Share Insurance Fund; managing the assets of failed credit unions; and providing emergency liquidity.

    The NCUA works to protect credit union members and consumers, raise awareness of potential frauds, facilitate access to affordable financial services, and educate consumers on the importance of savings and how they can improve their financial well-being.

    Stay up to date on the NCUA's activities by subscribing to the NCUA's Express messages. Read press releases, speeches, testimony, and Annual Reports. Register for upcoming conferences and events.

Breadcrumb
----------

1. [Home](https://ncua.gov/)
2. \> [Privacy](https://ncua.gov/privacy)

+

Website Privacy Policy
----------------------

Website Privacy Policy
======================

Search
------

Search keywords or topics to find answers

### Jump to...

Thank you for visiting our website and reviewing our website privacy policy (this policy applies to [www.ncua.gov,](https://ncua.gov/ "Go to the homepage") [www.MyCreditUnion.gov](https://www.mycreditunion.gov/ "Go to MyCreditUnion.gov"), and the Spanish versions of the sites).

Our website privacy policy is:

* You do not have to give us personal information to visit our websites.
* Our websites automatically collect non-personal information about our website visitors.
* Anywhere from our site that requests personally identifiable information (PII) such as submitting a form or signing up for an event, we tell you what we are collecting, why we are collecting it, and how we are going to use it. We only collect the minimum amount of PII to achieve the task and safeguard the information collected.
* We will not disclose, give, sell, or transfer any information about our website visitors, unless required to do so by law.

Below is more detailed information about aspects of our website privacy policy. If you have any questions about the NCUA’s privacy practices, please email [privacy@ncua.gov](mailto:privacy@ncua.gov "Send an email to the NCUA privacy official").

Privacy Policy
--------------

### Personal Information Voluntarily Given to the NCUA

Submitting personal information (name, address, telephone number, email address, etc.) is voluntary and is not required to access information on our website. However, you may choose to provide the NCUA with personal information -- for example by completing a form, or sending us an email. Before you do, there are a few things that we would like you to know:

We will use the information that you provide to respond to your message and/or help us get you the information or services you request, but doing so may involve multiple people (including other agencies) seeing the information that you provide.

We will maintain the information in accordance with the Privacy Act (as applicable) and will destroy the information in accordance with the Federal Records Act and records schedules approved by the National Archives and Records Administration.

Also, in some cases, the information may be subject to disclosure to a third party (for example, if required by a Freedom of Information Act request, court order, or Congressional access request, or if authorized by a Privacy Act System of Records Notice).

For more information, see:

### Non-Personal Information Automatically Collected and Stored

To improve the quality of our website services, we use Google’s Universal Analytics software to gather and temporarily store a variety of information about all of our website visitors. This happens automatically whenever someone visits our website. The information we collect about every website visitor includes:

* The date and time of your visit to our website;
* The pages and documents that you view on our website;
* The URL of the website that you visited prior to ours;
* The name of the domain that you use to access the Internet (for example, Verizon.com, if you are using a Verizon online account, or stanford.edu, if you are connecting from Stanford University’s domain);
* The type and version of your web browser and operating system;
* Your location at the time of your visit, down to the city-level; and
* Other more technical information, including the HTTP status code, Windows NT code, number of bytes sent, number of bytes received, duration (in seconds) to fulfill the request, server port number address, and protocol version.

[https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/ "View the Google Analytics Privacy Policy").

### Interactions with Children Online

The NCUA is committed to the protection of children’s online privacy. Although some sections of the NCUA’s websites offer educational content to children, we do not collect any personal information from any visitors of those sites.

### Links to Other Websites

Our websites sometimes contain links to other federal agencies, private organizations, and commercial entities. The NCUA is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of any non-NCUA websites, and providing a link to non-NCUA website is not intended to be an endorsement of the website or its content. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of every website that you visit.

### Visiting an Official NCUA Page on Third-Party Websites

We maintain accounts on third-party websites, such as social media sites, as tools to better interact with the public. We also have embedded applications from third-party websites on our sites. We use third-party websites, such as social media websites like Facebook and Twitter, to share information, engage in dialogue, and promote transparency and accountability. We do not use third-party websites to solicit or collect personal information from individuals.

The security and privacy policies of third-party websites apply to your activity on those sites. If you choose to post personal information on any public site, you do so at your own risk. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of all websites before using them and ensure that you understand how your information may be used (and to consider adjusting your privacy settings to your liking).

Here are the website privacy policies of the third-party websites on which the NCUA has office pages:

* [Facebook Data Use Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/ "View the Facebook policy (Link opens in new tab)")
* [LinkedIn Privacy Policy](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy "View the LinkedIn policy (Link opens in new tab)")
* [Twitter Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/privacy "View the Twitter policy (Link opens in new tab)")

### Social Media Comment Moderation

The NCUA welcomes comments from the public and provides the following guidance for participating in this forum. As a federal government agency, NCUA reminds all users that the conversations taking place on NCUA social media pages be courteous and in compliance with the summary guidance provided below.

The NCUA encourages robust discussion of policy issues and appreciates feedback from the public, but the agency reserves the right to delete comments for any of the following reasons:

* Violent, vulgar, obscene, profane, hateful, sexist, racist rhetoric, or other similarly inappropriate or unlawful comments
* Threats to or defamation of any person or organization
* Links to other websites
* Off-topic discussions
* The violation of the privacy of another individual
* Solicitations, advertisements, or endorsements of any financial, commercial, or non-governmental entity
* Suggesting or encouraging illegal activity
* Partisan political content, including solicitations of funds, comments promoting or opposing any political party or candidate for election to a political office, or promoting or opposing any ballot proposition
* Posting of Social Security numbers, phone numbers, email addresses, residential addresses, or personally identifiable information
* Repetitive posts copied and pasted by multiple users

Reporters or other media representatives should refrain from submitting questions to the NCUA here as comments. Instead, please reach out to the NCUA’s Office of External Affairs and Communications at 703.518.6330 or [oeacmail@ncua.gov](mailto:oeacmail@ncua.gov).

### Website Security

This site is maintained by the U.S. government. Unauthorized attempts to upload information and/or change information on this site are strictly prohibited under federal laws. You can be arrested and prosecuted for violating these laws.

For site security purposes and to ensure that our websites remain available to all users, we use software programs to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information or otherwise cause damage. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, no other attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits.

### Technical Information Collected Automatically

The NCUA website uses cookies to collect and analyze anonymous statistical data. This data helps the NCUA improve the NCUA website for users. The cookies only collect information about your NCUA website usage, and not you personally. The NCUA does not disclose the information collected unless required by law. The information is retained as outlined by the NCUA’s approved records schedules and as noted by the vendors below. The following types of cookies are used on the NCUA’s website:

**Tier 1 Cookies (Session Cookies)** are stored temporarily on your computer and deleted as soon as the browser is closed. NCUA sometimes uses these cookies to improve your experience by analyzing your usage of the NCUA website.

**Tier 2 Cookies (Persistent Cookies):** The NCUA uses “persistent cookie” technology such as Google Analytics and Microsoft Clarity to track your visit across the NCUA website. Persistent cookies allow the NCUA to create a more personalized experience for you.

**Google Analytics** collects non-identifying information (not personally identifiable information) such as the type of browser and the version of the browser you are using to visit our website; the date and time you visited the NCUA website, what pages you viewed on the NCUA website, the URL of the website that you visited prior to the NCUA’s website, the name of the domain that you use to access the Internet, your geographic location information (not your home address), and other more technical information, including the HTTP status code, Windows NT code, number of bytes sent and received, duration (in seconds) to fulfill the request, server port number addressed, and protocol version. _See_ [https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

**Microsoft Clarity** captures how you use and interact with the NCUA website through behavioral metrics, heatmaps, and session replay to customize the NCUA website to the NCUA users. Website usage data is captured using first and third-party cookies and other tracking technologies to determine the popularity of products/services and online activity. _See_ [https://clarity.microsoft.com/terms](https://clarity.microsoft.com/terms).

**Opt-Out Instructions:** You can set your computer website settings to reject cookies, and you will still be able to access the information on the NCUA website. The website may not be as customized or not function as efficiently without the use of cookies. To learn more about how to opt out of cookies, visit USA.gov Web Measurement and Customization [Opt-Out](https://www.usa.gov/optout-instructions).

Last modified on

05/29/24

**Stay Informed**

**Our Sites**

[

**MyCreditUnion.gov**

Trusted resource for consumer financial protection information.](https://mycreditunion.gov/ "Go to the MyCreditUnion.gov site")[

**Share Insurance**

Learn about credit union fund insurance.](https://ncua.gov/consumers/share-insurance-coverage "Go to the Share Insurance Coverage page")[

**Research a Credit Union**

View information for a specific credit union, download Call Reports, and request Financial Performance Reports.](https://mapping.ncua.gov/ResearchCreditUnion "Go to the Research a Credit Union site")[

**Credit Union Locator**

Find a credit union by address, credit union name, or charter number.](https://mapping.ncua.gov/ "Go to the Credit Union Locator site")
